1	1	George	George	0	6	NNP	PERSON
1	2	Washington	Washington	7	17	NNP	PERSON
1	3	was	be	18	21	VBD	O
1	4	the	the	22	25	DT	O
1	5	first	first	26	31	JJ	ORDINAL	1.0
1	6	President	president	32	41	NN	O
1	7	of	of	42	44	IN	O
1	8	the	the	45	48	DT	O
1	9	United	United	49	55	NNP	LOCATION
1	10	States	States	56	62	NNPS	LOCATION
1	11	,	,	63	64	,	O
1	12	who	who	65	68	WP	O
1	13	was	be	69	72	VBD	O
1	14	one	one	73	76	CD	NUMBER	1.0
1	15	of	of	77	79	IN	O
1	16	the	the	80	83	DT	O
1	17	Founding	found	84	92	VBG	O
1	18	Fathers	father	93	100	NNS	O
1	19	of	of	101	103	IN	O
1	20	the	the	104	107	DT	O
1	21	United	United	108	114	NNP	LOCATION
1	22	States	States	115	121	NNPS	LOCATION
1	23	.	.	122	123	.	O
2	1	He	he	125	127	PRP	O
2	2	drafted	draft	128	135	VBD	O
2	3	the	the	136	139	DT	O
2	4	Constitution	Constitution	140	152	NNP	O
2	5	and	and	153	156	CC	O
2	6	he	he	157	159	PRP	O
2	7	served	serve	160	166	VBD	O
2	8	two	two	167	170	CD	NUMBER	2.0
2	9	terms	term	171	176	NNS	O
2	10	in	in	177	179	IN	O
2	11	office	office	180	186	NN	O
2	12	.	.	187	188	.	O
3	1	Washington	Washington	190	200	NNP	LOCATION
3	2	was	be	201	204	VBD	O
3	3	born	bear	205	209	VBN	O
3	4	in	in	210	212	IN	O
3	5	Virginia	Virginia	213	221	NNP	LOCATION
3	6	where	where	222	227	WRB	O
3	7	his	he	228	231	PRP$	O
3	8	family	family	232	238	NN	O
3	9	owned	own	239	244	VBD	O
3	10	tobacco	tobacco	245	252	NN	O
3	11	plantations	plantation	253	264	NNS	O
3	12	and	and	265	268	CC	O
3	13	slaves	slave	269	275	NNS	O
3	14	.	.	276	277	.	O
4	1	After	after	279	284	IN	O
4	2	both	both	285	289	DT	O
4	3	his	he	290	293	PRP$	O
4	4	father	father	294	300	NN	O
4	5	and	and	301	304	CC	O
4	6	older	older	305	310	JJR	O
4	7	brother	brother	311	318	NN	O
4	8	died	die	319	323	VBD	O
4	9	when	when	324	328	WRB	O
4	10	he	he	329	331	PRP	O
4	11	was	be	332	335	VBD	O
4	12	young	young	336	341	JJ	O
4	13	,	,	342	343	,	O
4	14	he	he	344	346	PRP	O
4	15	became	become	347	353	VBD	O
4	16	personally	personally	354	364	RB	O
4	17	attached	attach	365	373	VBN	O
4	18	to	to	374	376	TO	O
4	19	William	William	377	384	NNP	PERSON
4	20	Fairfax	Fairfax	385	392	NNP	PERSON
4	21	,	,	393	394	,	O
4	22	who	who	395	398	WP	O
4	23	promoted	promote	399	407	VBD	O
4	24	his	he	408	411	PRP$	O
4	25	career	career	412	418	NN	O
4	26	.	.	419	420	.	O
5	1	George	George	422	428	NNP	PERSON
5	2	Washington	Washington	429	439	NNP	PERSON
5	3	opposed	oppose	440	447	VBD	O
5	4	slavery	slavery	448	455	NN	O
5	5	as	as	456	458	IN	O
5	6	he	he	459	461	PRP	O
5	7	viewed	view	462	468	VBD	O
5	8	it	it	469	471	PRP	O
5	9	as	as	472	474	IN	O
5	10	a	a	475	476	DT	O
5	11	potentially	potentially	477	488	RB	O
5	12	moral	moral	489	494	JJ	O
5	13	threat	threat	495	501	NN	O
5	14	to	to	502	504	TO	O
5	15	the	the	505	508	DT	O
5	16	unity	unity	509	514	NN	O
5	17	of	of	515	517	IN	O
5	18	the	the	518	521	DT	O
5	19	nation	nation	522	528	NN	O
5	20	.	.	529	530	.	O
6	1	When	when	532	536	WRB	O
6	2	Washington	Washington	537	547	NNP	LOCATION
6	3	married	marry	548	555	VBD	O
6	4	Martha	Martha	556	562	NNP	PERSON
6	5	Custis	Custis	563	569	NNP	PERSON
6	6	in	in	570	572	IN	O
6	7	1759	1759	573	577	CD	NUMBER	1759.0
6	8	,	,	578	579	,	O
6	9	he	he	580	582	PRP	O
6	10	owned	own	583	588	VBD	O
6	11	at	at	589	591	IN	O
6	12	least	least	592	597	JJS	O
6	13	36	36	598	600	CD	NUMBER	>=36.0
6	14	slaves	slave	601	607	NNS	O
6	15	,	,	608	609	,	O
6	16	then	then	610	614	RB	O
6	17	his	he	615	618	PRP$	O
6	18	wife	wife	619	623	NN	O
6	19	brought	bring	624	631	VBD	O
6	20	85	85	632	634	CD	NUMBER	85.0
6	21	slaves	slave	635	641	NNS	O
6	22	inherited	inherit	642	651	VBN	O
6	23	from	from	652	656	IN	O
6	24	her	she	657	660	PRP$	O
6	25	late	late	661	665	JJ	O
6	26	husband	husband	666	673	NN	O
6	27	's	's	674	676	POS	O
6	28	estate	estate	677	683	NN	O
6	29	.	.	684	685	.	O
7	1	They	they	687	691	PRP	O
7	2	had	have	692	695	VBD	O
7	3	135	135	696	699	CD	NUMBER	135.0
7	4	slaves	slave	700	706	NNS	O
7	5	in	in	707	709	IN	O
7	6	1772	1772	710	714	CD	NUMBER	1772.0
7	7	,	,	715	716	,	O
7	8	all	all	717	720	DT	O
7	9	of	of	721	723	IN	O
7	10	them	they	724	728	PRP	O
7	11	placed	place	729	735	VBD	O
7	12	at	at	736	738	IN	O
7	13	his	he	739	742	PRP$	O
7	14	plantations	plantation	743	754	NNS	O
7	15	at	at	755	757	IN	O
7	16	Mount	Mount	758	763	NNP	LOCATION
7	17	Vernon	Vernon	764	770	NNP	LOCATION
7	18	.	.	771	772	.	O
8	1	The	the	774	777	DT	O
8	2	Washington	Washington	778	788	NNP	LOCATION
8	3	Monument	Monument	789	797	NNP	O
8	4	,	,	798	799	,	O
8	5	George	George	800	806	NNP	ORGANIZATION
8	6	Washington	Washington	807	817	NNP	ORGANIZATION
8	7	University	University	818	828	NNP	ORGANIZATION
8	8	,	,	829	830	,	O
8	9	and	and	831	834	CC	O
8	10	George	George	835	841	NNP	PERSON
8	11	Washington	Washington	842	852	NNP	PERSON
8	12	Masonic	Masonic	853	860	NNP	ORGANIZATION
8	13	National	National	861	869	NNP	ORGANIZATION
8	14	Memorial	Memorial	870	878	NNP	ORGANIZATION
8	15	,	,	879	880	,	O
8	16	have	have	881	885	VBP	O
8	17	their	they	886	891	PRP$	O
8	18	name	name	892	896	NN	O
8	19	given	give	897	902	VBN	O
8	20	in	in	903	905	IN	O
8	21	honor	honor	906	911	NN	O
8	22	of	of	912	914	IN	O
8	23	George	George	915	921	NNP	PERSON
8	24	Washington	Washington	922	932	NNP	PERSON
8	25	.	.	933	934	.	O		
