1	1	Chanel	Chanel	0	6	NNP	ORGANIZATION
1	2	is	be	7	9	VBZ	O
1	3	a	a	10	11	DT	O
1	4	French	french	12	18	JJ	O
1	5	company	company	19	26	NN	O
1	6	owned	own	27	32	VBN	O
1	7	by	by	33	35	IN	O
1	8	Wertheimer	Wertheimer	36	46	NNP	PERSON
1	9	brothers	brother	47	55	NNS	O
1	10	.	.	56	57	.	O
2	1	They	they	59	63	PRP	O
2	2	are	be	64	67	VBP	O
2	3	grandsons	grandson	68	77	NNS	O
2	4	of	of	78	80	IN	O
2	5	Pierre	Pierre	81	87	NNP	PERSON
2	6	Wertheimer	Wertheimer	88	98	NNP	PERSON
2	7	,	,	99	100	,	O
2	8	who	who	101	104	WP	O
2	9	was	be	105	108	VBD	O
2	10	a	a	109	110	DT	O
2	11	business	business	111	119	NN	O
2	12	partner	partner	120	127	NN	O
2	13	of	of	128	130	IN	O
2	14	Gabrielle	Gabrielle	131	140	NNP	PERSON
2	15	Chanel	Chanel	141	147	NNP	PERSON
2	16	.	.	148	149	.	O
3	1	Coco	Coco	151	155	NNP	PERSON
3	2	Chanel	Chanel	156	162	NNP	PERSON
3	3	,	,	163	164	,	O
3	4	how	how	165	168	WRB	O
3	5	she	she	169	172	PRP	O
3	6	famously	famously	173	181	RB	O
3	7	known	know	182	187	VBN	O
3	8	in	in	188	190	IN	O
3	9	fashion	fashion	191	198	NN	O
3	10	business	business	199	207	NN	O
3	11	,	,	208	209	,	O
3	12	designed	design	210	218	VBN	O
3	13	elegance	elegance	219	227	NN	O
3	14	dress	dress	228	233	NN	O
3	15	for	for	234	237	IN	O
3	16	models	model	238	244	NNS	O
3	17	and	and	245	248	CC	O
3	18	actresses	actress	249	258	NNS	O
3	19	.	.	259	260	.	O
4	1	House	House	262	267	NNP	O
4	2	of	of	268	270	IN	O
4	3	Chanel	Chanel	271	277	NNP	O
4	4	,	,	278	279	,	O
4	5	her	she	280	283	PRP	O
4	6	fashion	fashion	284	291	NN	O
4	7	brand	brand	292	297	NN	O
4	8	,	,	298	299	,	O
4	9	is	be	300	302	VBZ	O
4	10	most	most	303	307	RBS	O
4	11	famous	famous	308	314	JJ	O
4	12	for	for	315	318	IN	O
4	13	its	its	319	322	PRP	O
4	14	little	little	323	329	JJ	O
4	15	black	black	330	335	JJ	O
4	16	dress	dress	336	341	NN	O
4	17	,	,	342	343	,	O
4	18	the	the	344	347	DT	O
4	19	perfume	perfume	348	355	NN	O
4	20	No.	no.	356	359	NN	O
4	21	5	5	360	361	CD	NUMBER	5.0
4	22	de	de	362	364	NNP	O
4	23	Chanel	Chanel	365	371	NNP	O
4	24	,	,	372	373	,	O
4	25	and	and	374	377	CC	O
4	26	the	the	378	381	DT	O
4	27	Chanel	Chanel	382	388	NNP	O
4	28	Suit	Suit	389	393	NNP	O
4	29	.	.	394	395	.	O
5	1	It	it	397	399	PRP	O
5	2	was	be	400	403	VBD	O
5	3	originated	originate	404	414	VBN	O
5	4	in	in	415	417	IN	O
5	5	1909	1909	418	422	CD	NUMBER	1909.0
5	6	,	,	423	424	,	O
5	7	when	when	425	429	WRB	O
5	8	she	she	430	433	PRP	O
5	9	opened	open	434	440	VBD	O
5	10	a	a	441	442	DT	O
5	11	shop	shop	443	447	NN	O
5	12	at	at	448	450	IN	O
5	13	160	160	451	454	CD	NUMBER	160.0
5	14	Boulevard	Boulevard	455	464	NNP	O
5	15	Malesherbes	Malesherbes	465	476	NNP	O
5	16	,	,	477	478	,	O
5	17	the	the	479	482	DT	O
5	18	ground	ground	483	489	NN	O
5	19	floor	floor	490	495	NN	O
5	20	of	of	496	498	IN	O
5	21	the	the	499	502	DT	O
5	22	Parisian	parisian	503	511	JJ	O
5	23	flat	flat	512	516	NN	O
5	24	of	of	517	519	IN	O
5	25	Etienne	Etienne	520	527	NNP	PERSON
5	26	Balsan	Balsan	528	534	NNP	PERSON
5	27	,	,	535	536	,	O
5	28	of	of	537	539	IN	O
5	29	whom	whom	540	544	WP	O
5	30	she	she	545	548	PRP	O
5	31	was	be	549	552	VBD	O
5	32	mistress	mistress	553	561	JJ	O
5	33	.	.	562	563	.	O
